<resources>
    <string name="copyright_title">%1$s</string>
    <string name="copyright_detail">Version %2$s, %3$s
\nCopyright &#169; 2016 %1$s
\na nelladragon.com app.
</string>

    <string name="terms_of_use_title">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">IMPORTANT: PLEASE READ THIS LICENSE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE.
\n
\n1. LICENSE
\n
\nBy receiving, opening the file package, and/or using %3$s %2$s("Software")
containing this software, you agree that this End User License Agreement(EULA) is a
legally binding and valid contract and agree to be bound by it. You agree to abide by
the intellectual property laws and all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
\n
\nUnless you have a different license agreement signed by %1$s ("Author") your use of this software
indicates your acceptance of this license agreement and warranty.
\n
\nSubject to the terms of this Agreement, the author grants to you a limited, non-exclusive,
non-transferable license, without right to sub-license, to use the software in
accordance with this Agreement and any other written agreement with the author. The author
does not transfer the title of the software to you; the license granted to you is
not a sale. This agreement is a binding legal agreement between the author and the
purchasers or users of the software.
\n
\nIf you do not agree to be bound by this agreement, remove the software from your
device now.
\n
\n2. DISTRIBUTION
\n
\nThe software and the license herein granted shall not be copied, shared, distributed,
re-sold, offered for re-sale, transferred or sub-licensed in whole or in part except that you
may make one copy for archive purposes only. For information about redistribution of
this software please contact the author.
\n
\n3. USER AGREEMENT
\n
\n3.1 Use
\n
\nThis software is free, though a donation for use is appreciated. You can use this software
on as many devices as you like for free.
\n
\n3.2 Use Restrictions
\n
\nYou shall use the software in compliance with all applicable laws
and not for any unlawful purpose. Without limiting the foregoing, use, display
or distribution of the software together with material that is pornographic, racist,
vulgar, obscene, defamatory, libelous, abusive, promoting hatred, discriminating or
displaying prejudice based on religion, ethnic heritage, race, sexual
orientation or age is strictly prohibited.
\n
\n3.3 Copyright Restriction
\n
\nThis Software contains copyrighted material, trade secrets and other proprietary
material. You shall not, and shall not attempt to, modify, reverse engineer,
disassemble or decompile this software. Nor can you create any derivative works or
other works that are based upon or derived from this software in whole or in part.
\n
\nThe author\'s name, logo and graphics file that represents this software shall
not be used in any way to promote products developed with this software. The
author retains sole and exclusive ownership of all right, title and interest
in and to this software and all Intellectual Property rights relating thereto.
\n
\nCopyright law and international copyright treaty provisions protect all parts of
this software , products and services. No program, code, part, image, audio sample,
or text may be copied or used in any way by the user except as intended within the
bounds of the single user program. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are
reserved for the author.
\n
\n3.4 Limitation of Responsibility
\n
\nYou will indemnify, hold harmless, and defend Peter Robinson, his agents and
distributors against any and all claims, proceedings, demand and costs resulting
from or in any way connected with your use of this software.
\n
\nIn no event (including, without limitation, in the event of negligence) will
the author, his agents or distributors be liable for any consequential,
incidental, indirect, special or punitive damages whatsoever (including, without
limitation, damages for loss of profits, loss of use, business interruption, loss
of information or data, or pecuniary loss), in connection with or arising out of
or related to this Agreement, this software or the use or inability to use this
software or the furnishing, performance or use of any other matters hereunder
whether based upon contract, tort or any other theory including negligence.
\n
\nThe author\'s entire liability, without exception, is limited to the customers\'
reimbursement of the purchase price of the Software (maximum being the lesser of the
amount paid by you and the suggested retail price as listed by Peter Robinson ) in
exchange for the return of the product, all copies, registration papers and manuals,
and all materials that constitute a transfer of license from the customer back to the author.
\n
\n3.5 Warranties
\n
\nExcept as expressly stated in writing, the author makes no representation or
warranties in respect of this Software and expressly excludes all other warranties,
expressed or implied, oral or written, including, without limitation, any implied
warranties of merchantable quality or fitness for a particular purpose.
\n
\n3.6 Governing Law
\n
\nThis Agreement shall be governed by the law of the Australia applicable therein. You
hereby irrevocably attorn and submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts
of Australia therefrom. If any provision shall be considered unlawful, void or
otherwise unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this
License and not affect the validity and enforceability of any other provisions.
\n
\n3.7 Termination
\n
\nAny failure to comply with the terms and conditions of this Agreement will result in
automatic and immediate termination of this license. Upon termination of this license
granted herein for any reason, you agree to immediately cease use of this software and
destroy all copies of this software supplied under this Agreement. The financial
obligations incurred by you shall survive the expiration or termination of this license.
\n
\n4. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY
\n
\nTHIS SOFTWARE AND THE ACCOMPANYING FILES ARE SOLD "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES AS
TO PERFORMANCE OR MERCHANTABILITY OR ANY OTHER WARRANTIES WHETHER EXPRESSED OR
IMPLIED. THIS DISCLAIMER CONCERNS ALL FILES GENERATED AND EDITED BY this software AS WELL.
\n
\n5. CONSENT OF USE OF DATA
\n
\nYou agree that the author may collect and use information gathered in any manner
as part of the product support services provided to you, if any, related to this software.
The author may also use this information to provide notices to you which may be
of use or interest to you.
</string>



    <string name="open_source_title">Open Source Content</string>
    <string name="open_source_common">This page lists open source material used in the software.
\n
\nDegaws font is from http://www.studiotypo.com/ and is free for "personal use". I have asked
the authors if "personal use" equates to a "free app", and thus far have had no reply.
</string>


    <string name="open_source_specific">REPLACE ME: open_source_specific</string>
</resources>
